Hello hello everyone I am Varsha with you and today
we will talk about topper policies and super topper
policies let's start
whenever you buy a policy
you always have to select a deductible amount
what is the deductible amount that you have to first pay on your pocket whether it is
a corporate policy
or you have a parcel policy from anywhere you have to pay that
amount on yourself first only
after that you can use your policy
now let's talk
what is the difference between policy and super policy
so first let's talk about topper policy your policies are that for all the claims that
come to you throughout the year your
deductible amount will be first then your top
up will start that means whenever any of your
claims comes first you had chosen your deductible i.e.
2 lakh rupees 3 lakh rupees
first you will have to pay that amount yourself or
keep it in your nutrition policy and if
any amount comes on top of that that is your deductible
for example is 2 lakh rupees and your claim has gone up to
5 lakh rupees then first apply the amount
You have to take the amount from your pocket or from your policy,
which is ₹3 above, you
can use that policy from this, so in this way, for every
claim, you will have to make 2 lakhs from
your pocket from your personal policy,
after that the company deductible, the policy will be activated from above, after that
you will show the bill to the company, after that the
amount will be paid to the company, now talking about super top up, in this
you have to present it only in the first claim in the whole year, you can directly
use your super top up, so for example,
suppose your first time claim is ₹
5,000 or
13 lakh or deductible, then you have given ₹3 as deductible,
from your own policy up to 2 lakh above that in your pocket, the
company will give you super top up message,
after that at the same time if any claim
comes again, whether it is of ₹2 lakh or it is your
salary, the super top up you had taken is
₹1000000, then according to the second
₹10, then the entire company will pay you,
you will not need to pay anything.
If we talk about whether it is
important to take this policy, then for this I have
already made a video, you should first watch its first
part because I had
already told in the support that
why policies should be taken, why
policies are very important, whether all the things for taking these policies have
increased in the pot, then
I have given you the link of its first
part in the link below, so
if you have not seen that video yet, then
please click on the link and
check that video also and that is why I
always recommend that whenever you buy a
policy, then always choose the topper policy, it is better
for you
because you have to pay the deductible amount only once,
you do
not need to pay the deductible amount again and again in every plan, so it is mostly right,
for us you have
compared many companies and regarding topper policies, which
company gives a good plan,
what features does it give in PowerPlay,
I have given two such companies  I have brought their
top up lines which I found better,
I liked their Super Power Plants more
and their PM Mumbai's features are also
good, so today we will talk
about their features, I plan, we will
compare both of them, then you
must tell me in the comment section
after watching the entire video that after watching the features,
2 p.m.  After checking, which
policy seems better to you? These
two companies are the
Health Medical Shop Super Top Up of the individual and health insurance company.
One is this plan, which differentiates itself from others.
Super Splendor of Star Health Insurance Company. So, both of these are
super topper policies. Now, if I
compare both of them, let's track which one is better.
First of all, we will talk about the
premium. Because the same is important
in this policy. As I always
tell you, every time in the first policy, and
in this plan, I will tell you that
your premium is very less in topper policies. So,
first of all, we will check how much the premium is. So, I have brought the
difference in the premium between the two. I have
calculated the premium between 2016,
which is your one flavor. I have calculated their premium. So, let's
talk about the premium of Adams in both the policies.
First, let's check the premium of HDFC Ergo.
If you have
selected a deductible of Rs 3 lakh
and you have selected a sum assured of Rs 10,
that is, if any of the policies are covered under this policy,  ₹3 you can pay
from your pocket for your personal qualities
and up to seven lakh rupees after that ₹10
companies will show from this policy
Super Top Order Sinus In so
you will pay its premium after husband Said The
right to adult clothes in this case will be
your premium Along with this now let's talk about
Star Health in Star Health
if you are using Super Splendor with deductible of
3 lakh rupees Postal table you are
applying Someshwar is not raped in
this near road ₹1000000 is some time
more it will notice ₹3 up my
tablet ₹1000000 cup semi wide and
you are paying its premium it was soft you are
seeing the difference how much difference is
incomplete I provide you better quality then it is of
10 lakh
and this time ₹100 and then its premium when
cream this cost
quick is a better company Teachers
talk we have talked about premium so
now let's see in features which  This is a good
company, your hospitalization will be covered
in both the companies, so if you
want a recoverable hospitalization, it is mandatory, it is covered in both, there is
no typing, your room rent is
single and AC room, there is no topic in both,
if we talk about free hospitalization, then
your free hospitalization is
30 days, but now
in Star Help, you have sixteen years, if we
talk about post graduation, then your AC is
60 days, but Star Health is 190 days,
apart from that, let's talk about
day care, in your Star Health, the
warranty of all day treatment is done
by modern technology, from
there you can get old AC and treatment
of Economics and Hal, but
in your HDFC, only 119th treatment, your
cover entries can be made, both entries have been used,
you can buy this policy,
if your age is
below 65, you
can buy the policy in HDFC as well as
in Star Health, and
if you want a child, you can also add April
in this policy, from nine to one.
Yours will be of twenty three years in SDSC and
90171 your child will be up to 25 years. Let's
talk about Star Help waiting period. If
you have any accident, then
this reference of pride of the lineage will be cleared from 30 days
in both the companies. Now let's talk about slow
growing diseases, friends, your STD will be
cleared only after 2 years in this plan
but yours will be covered in Star Health in
between. In this plan, your after one
year will be covered like your diseases like spondylitis, piles,
cataract, coriander, joint replacement, these
diseases will increase after a moment
but in strange case, after 2 years, news
Priya West Indies, you already have any disease,
VPN, you have thyroid disease, you are already
doing a policy, in HDFC you will have to wait for 3 years,
after 3 years you
can claim for it, but if we talk about Star Help, then
Star Health or your Point
Best, your after one year can be cleared only after a moment.
You
talk about medical test for printing disease before doing the
policy.  For this you will have to get a medical test done. So
if you are paid by check
then in such a situation or definitely if you are
from 15 then you will have to get a medical test done. Now there is
no medical test, if there is anything then
you can have a medical test here, a
pre-medical test. After that, if we talk about the policy, then
this medical test will also be
remembered. Apart from that, there are many other
features like you will get air ambulance
in it.
If you order low-cost Star Health, then it will get
two Planets Halke Super
Setup, one Silver Plane, one Round
Planet Police Silver Prana Math,
because Silver Plane is definitely a topic
policy, that means you will have to pay a
deductible for every claim, so always be
on the lookout, if you check then
Super Surplus Minute Coldplay is one cycle only. The
premium that I have mentioned is for the Round Plane
only, so it is cheaper. If there is
no Golden Plan, then only Golden will decide
your topper. Perfectly, you will have to pay the
deductible in one time. There will be
no need to pay again and again. So
let's go and describe the delivery expenses.
Definitely, I liked this delivery extension very much.
In this, the
pregnancy maternity coverage that we normally see,
delivery expenses, when we check it, then the
feature that we see in the company group,
for that, one has to pay a very good extra premium,
it is a very expensive plan,
apart from that, you can also get
delivery covered after pregnancy, now you can get delivery cover after two years, the
idea is like this,
but here you
can get delivery cover as well as maternity cover after twelve
months, that is, after one year, your maternity will be
covered up to Rs. 250,000, if you have a
normal delivery, the company will cover the expenses up to Rs. 50,000, so
this is a very good feature, I found it to be a great feature,
apart from that, you are covered for organ donor,
you will also get best quarter recharge benefits in it, the above
mentioned policy does
not give any recharge benefit, but there is a recharge
benefit in this, the decision is that if the sum assured of Rs. 10
lakh is fully exhausted after taking the policy, then for that, those
companies will also charge you some amount,
that is different times.
According to the insurance, you should check once whether it is costing
you Rs. 5000 or avoid it for some time,
so this time you will have to chant,
this is some comparison
between both the companies, I have already
told you about the other aspects,
both of you have Ten Thousand Plus,
your network hospitals,
one more thing I would like to tell you about both these companies is that the
claims are settled through these only, there is
no TPA, there is no third party, these will be your
previous hospitals, so it is a
very good company, your TPA in HDFC Ergo is
such and I am your
TPA and the claims are settled through your OTP, that is
why they are not settled, so
you will have to see both these
things also, you should decide which one is right for both the companies, I have
told you the hard work,
after looking at both the companies, now decide which one is right,
whatever you feel,
tell me by commenting in the comment section that this is
company based so that other
people also get to know about it after reading the comments  Which
company is better, okay, so that's all for today's
video, if you liked the video then do
like, subscribe to this channel
and share this video,
thank you.